The files placed in this folder were originally found in various folders within the Python 3.8 installation folder.


They have been moved here for portability, just in case a BrailleR function needs to call them and cannot find them in the user's system, possibly because they are not located in a folder that is in the system path settings.

No claim for ownership, maintenance, etc. are made by anyone linked with the BrailleR package.

The current list of files (and the corresponding comment from the Python38 readme.txt file) includes:

crlf.py			Change CRLF line endings to LF (Windows to Unix)
google.py		Open a webbrowser with Google
lfcr.py			Change LF line endings to CRLF (Unix to Windows)
untabify.py		Replace tabs with spaces in argument files

